(Qexample) CARL: Hi, come and take a seat.
JULIE: Thank you.
CARL: My name's Carl Rogers and l'm one of the doctors here at the Total Health Clinic. CARL：
So I understand this is your first visit to the clinic?
JULIE: Yes, it is. JULIE：
CARL: OK, well I hope you'll be very happy with the service you receive here. CARL：
So if it's aright with you I'll take a few details to help me give you the best possible service.
JULIE: Sure. JULIE：
CARL: So can I check first of all that we have the correct personal details for you? CARL：
(Q1) So your full name is Julie Anne Garcia?
JULIE: That's correct. JULIE：
[Q1答案句] CARL: Perfect. And can I have a contact phone number?JULIE: It's 219 442 9785
⭐
(Q2) [Q2答案句] CARL: OK, and then can I just check that we have the correct date of birth?JULIE: October tenth, 1992.
CARL: Oh, I actually have 1991, l'll just correct that now. CARL：
Right, so that's all good.
(Q3) Now I just need just a few more personal details...
do you have an occupation, either full-time or part-time?
JULIE: Yes, I work full-time in Esterhazy's you know, the restaurant chain. JULIE：
[Q3答案句： manager， 有干扰项（时间干扰）] I started off as a waitress there a few years ago and l'm a manager now.
CARL: Oh I know them, yeah, they're down on 114th Street, aren't they? CARL：
JULIE: That's right. JULIE：
CARL: Yeah, l've been there a few times. CARL：
I just love their salads.
JULIE: That's good to hear. JULIE：
(Q4) CARL: Right, so one more thing I need to know before we talk about why you're here, Julie, and that's the name of your insurance company.
[Q4答案句] JULIE: lt's Cawley Life Insurance, that's C-A-W-L-E-Y.
CARL: Excellent, thank you so much.
(Q5) GARL: Now Julie, let's look at how we can help you.
So tell me a little about what brought you here today.
[Q5答案句： pain原词， left语序调换，所以要跟名词] JULIE: Well, I've been getting a pain in my knee, the left one. JULIE：
Not very serious at first, but it's gotten worse, so I thought I ought to see someone about it.
CARL: That's certainly the right decision. CARL：
(Q6) So how long have you been aware of this pain?
ls it just a few days, or is it longer than that?
JULIE: Longer. JULIE：
[Q6答案句] lt's been worse for the last couple of days, but it's three weeks since I first noticed it.
It came on quite gradually though, so I kind of ignored it at first.
(Q7) CARL: And have you taken any medication yourself, or treated it in anyway? CARL：
JULIE: Yeah, l've been taking medication to deal with the pain, Tylenol, and that works OK for a few hours. JULIE：
But I don't like to keep taking it.
CARL: OK. CARL：
And what about heat treatment?
Have you tried applying heat at all?
JULIE: No, but I have been using ice on it for the last few days. JULIE：
CARL: And does that seem to help the pain at all? CARL：
JULIE: A little, yes. JULIE：
CARL: Good. CARL：
Now you look as if you're quite fit normally?
JULIE: I am, yes. JULIE：
CARL: So do you do any sport on a regular basis? CARL：
[Q7答案句] JULIE: Yes, I play a lot of tennis. I belong to a club so I go there a lot.
⭐
(Q8) I'm quite competitive so I enjoy that side of it as well as the exercise.
But I haven't gone since this started.
CARL: Sure. CARL：
And do you do any other types of exercise?
[Q8答案句+干扰项（but排除掉)] JULIE: Yeah, I sometimes do a little swimming❌, but usually just when I'm on vacation.But normally I go 【running✅】 a few times a week, maybe three or four times.
CARL: Hmm. CARL：
(Q9) So your legs are getting quite a pounding.
But you haven't had any problems up to now?
[Q9答案句+干扰项（legs）， 跟同替 hurt=injure 能识别] JULIE: No, not with my legs. I did have an accident last year when I slipped and hurt my shoulder, but that's better now.
CARL: Excellent. CARL：
(Q10) And do you have any allergies?
JULIE: No, none that I'm aware of. JULIE：
[Q10答案句： vitamin & that's all , 反向替换 - 语义 = no ... apart from ...] CARL: And do you take any medication on a regular basis?JULIE: Well, I take vitamins but that's all I'm generally very healthy.
CARL: OK, well let's have a closer look and see what might be causing this problem. CARL：
If you can just get up...